solve360.com 2004-04-16

# 

Last modified: May 4, 2001

_Solve360 Privacy Policy_ **Children.** The Solve360™ Service (the "Service") is not available to children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, under no circumstances should you send us any personally identifying information, attempt to register or otherwise utilize the Service. If parents believe their child (any age under 18) has accessed our Service without their permission, they can contact our Customer Service department listed at the end of this notice. **Disclosure to Third Parties.** We will not give third parties individually identifiable information about Users except for the limited purposes described below.

  1. In accordance with the Terms of Service of the Service, whenever it is necessary or appropriate to comply with the law or legal process, to protect our systems and customers, or to ensure the integrity and operation of our business and systems
  2. We have the express permission of the User, such as provided in the Terms of Service
  3. As required to process commercial transactions
  4. Share aggregated statistical data with our business partners and the general public. For example, we may disclose that 10% of our Users live in California.

**Information Collected From Users.** We collect the following information from Users through our online registration form:

  * Username
  * Password
  * Full Name
  * Alternate contact email address
  * Pager email (optional)
  * Time Zone
  * Country
  * How they heard about us
  * Background graphic preference

**Questionnaires, Surveys and Profile Data**. We may offer optional questionnaires and surveys to our users for such purposes as collecting demographic information or assessing users' interests and needs. The use of the information collected will be explained in the survey itself. **Aggregate Statistical Information.** We may collect aggregated statistical information for purposes of improving the Service. This data does not contain personally identifying information, such as name or email address. **Internal Uses.** We use data collected on the Service to: 1) provide customer service, and 2) improve the Service. We give access to individually identifiable information about our Users only to Norada employees on a need to know basis to fulfill customer service requests. **Internet Information.** We use IP addresses to analyze trends, help diagnose problems with our computer systems, administer the Service, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. **Use of Cookies.** This Service uses cookies to establish a login session, set User tailored options and optionally to save a User's password so they do not have to re-enter it each time they authenticate to the Service. This feature is specific to the particular browser that the User has installed on their computer. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information other than is stated here. Web browsers are designed to accept cookies. By default, most browsers are configured to accept cookies without notifying the User. Cookies are safe and most web sites use them frequently. Browsers can be configured to refuse cookies, but this Service will not work without them. **Opting Out.** At the end of the registration process, a new User may elect to be excluded from any surveys or product announcements. A User who later decides not to receive email notifications for product announcements may choose to opt out by changing their preferences in the User Options section. **Transaction Information.** To process commercial transactions, we collect information related to each transaction, such as the amount and the necessary identifying information, including the credit card information or email addresses of the parties involved. **Corrections and Updates.** Users can update their personal information at anytime. This is accomplished online in the User Options section. In some cases, it may be necessary to contact our Customer Service department listed at the end of this notice. **Deactivation.** Users may terminate an account by sending a written request to our Customer Service department listed at the end of this notice. **Notification of Changes.** This policy may be revised over time. We will post those changes prominently so that the Users will receive reasonable notice to these changes and know what information we gather, how we might use that information, and whether we will disclose it to anyone. Please check this site regularly for information about revisions to our Privacy Policy. **Official Language.** All Services to be provided, all obligations of Norada, and all communications between the parties with respect to this Agreement will be done in the English language. The parties to this Privacy Policy confirm and agree that this Policy, and all related documentation will be in the English language. Web pages which are translated from English to other popular languages of the World may contain errors / omissions. If for any reason the translated text is incorrect, or misleading, the English text shall be deemed as the correct, original, and official notice. **Contacting the Web Site.** If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

Norada Corporation  
Customer Service Department  
Email: [feedback@solve360.com](mailto:feedback@solve360.com)  
Phone: 403.630.9984

Inquires are processed Monday to Friday from 9am and 5pm MST 

###
